[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Disclaimer: Characters, locations, and all depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only; viewer discretion is advised]
I'm sorry, Pai.
Wan, it's been so many takes.
Focus only on the person you're acting with.
Only look at me.
Only listen to me.
Stay with me.
What are your feelings toward Third?
Is it still the same?
Try to keep your distance from him.
- Whoa! - Third!
Wan!
You hit him for real?
I'm sorry.
Chew me out however you want.
I'm here to take responsibility.
Were you being gaslit?
And you still believed that?
I don't know.
Still deciding.
Then, I'll give you as much time as you need
because you...
are stuck with me for a long time.
Ugh!
Am I your bestie or something?!
What the heck are you doing?
What did I do?
Right, don't you have a schedule today?
I don't.
Cher told me to take a break.
Look what I've gotta do here.
Next time, if you're not willing to be here,
you don't have to come.
Hey... no.
I honestly came to apologize.
Have you left yet, Third?
We're meeting at 1 P.M.
I'm heading out.
Want me to give you a ride?
I'd probably still make it in time.
It's fine.
I rode my motorcycle here.
What's on your schedule?
How can you still call yourself a Nine fan?
How come you don't know your bias's public schedule?
Let's go.
Or maybe...
you'd rather wait for me here?
Whoever wants to stay can stay.
I'm not staying.
Peace out...
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
[Mr. Fanboy Series]
[Episode 5: "Now It Makes Sense"]
[SOUP]
Hello, hello.
Please make way for them.
Thank you.
- Hello, Nine. - Oops?
You're Ball, right?
- I thought that was about the World Cup. - Force of habit.
Hello.
Right, hello.
Let's do an interview, shall we?
Of course.
Absolutely.
- Ball, right? - Be right back.
- Ballie! - Right, you're Ballie.
Thank you.
Ooh...
I'm sorry.
You're good.
Uh...
excuse me,
have we met at other events before?
Uh...
maybe we have.
I come to events like this quite often.
But you sound so familiar.
You sound so much like Wan.
No... I'm not him.
I'm not.
Uh...
Please excuse me.
Girl...
- What? - I think this is Wan.
It's definitely him.
Don't you think?
Huh?
And why would he be here?
If he comes, he's getting a piece of me
for punching my baby boy in the mouth.
Then, allow me to ask about the hottest topic right now.
Recently, some news has surfaced that you and Wan
got so immersed in your roles
that you ended up getting into a real fight on set.
Right,
let me make this clear.
Wan and I were not fighting.
It was one of the scenes in the pilot.
And him punching me
was an accident on set,
and the producer has released a statement to clarify it.
Actually,
I wasn't there when it happened,
but when I found out
about a miscue on set,
I was a little shocked.
So I asked Third if he was alright,
but he said he was fine,
just a small wound at the corner of his mouth.
Huh?!
A wound at the corner of his mouth?!
Exactly.
He had a wound?
Oh, just a tiny one.
Yeah,
but I treated his wound
and took him home.
You took him home?!
Yes,
I did take him home.
Uh, anyway...
I do think
it was an honest mistake
because Wan is still so new.
That's why
the accident happened on set,
as the producer explained in the statement.
Mm...
but people on social media
seem to be really upset with Wan.
I think that people on X
have gotten it so wrong
without knowing the whole truth.
I don't think this is fair to Wan.
And everyone working behind the scenes
has been working so hard.
Also, Wan and I are getting along well.
Uh...
that's right.
So, uh...
Anyway, everyone,
please understand.
Lastly,
please look forward to our series,
'The Deep Between Us.'
Right now, the pilot is about to launch.
I'm so excited,
and you are too, right?
Anyway...
please give us your support.
Yes, please stay tuned.
Please do.
- Thank you. - Please stay tuned.
Yes, thank you.
Sunny, have you seen this?
"Third's betraying Nine.
He's so disrespectful to his own partner.
He doesn't even thank Nine.
Nine seems so worried about Third,
but all he does is protect someone who hurts him.
How could he forget the person beside him?
What an awful move.
So disrespectful to Nine.
More importantly, the cute moments are nonexistent.
That man spits those out when he's being fed."
"See his eyes when he's talking about Wan?
With that sweet, sweet look,
why don't you change your partner already, you bastard?!"
Ooh...
That "bastard" part wasn't there.
I added it.
Mama,
let's find something sweet to eat.
How does one turn a crisis into an even more fucked-up crisis?
With utter stupidity, I guess.
Your mom's gonna come chew your ass out,
Richie Rich.
Don't listen too much to what he says.
Let it go.
Go get changed now so you can go home.
Wan.
Hey!
Don't mess with my stuff!
Are you nuts?
Aren't you afraid you'll get caught?
You realize you can't go support your bias like you did, right?
I do...
I just happened to pass by.
I'm serious, Wan.
Even if your fanbase is completely abandoned
and has no photos of Nine to post,
you can't go support your bias like you did.
I'm saying this
because I'm worried.
What?!
You're already involved in a drama.
Do you even know you're about to be dragged into another one?
Here.
I think that people on X
have gotten it so wrong...
[Anyone else feel that tension?]
without knowing the whole truth.
I don't think this is fair to Wan.
And everyone working behind the scenes...
Third really put you under fire.
And what are the comments saying?
Nine's fans are cussing Third out like crazy.
And there's one more thing.
Fans have started a ThirdWan fanbase on X.
But why?
Well, when Third was talking about you,
he was grinning from ear to ear.
There's chemistry;
how could they resist shipping?
You're screwed, dude.
Ugh...
Nine's gonna be so mad at me...
Since news has spread about the miscue
on the set of The Deep Between Us,
it has sparked a backlash against Wan.
Your companies and I have discussed it
and decided that...
for the sake of our set's image,
we're gonna have the cast members
spend some time...
living together.
Won't this affect us when we start filming?
We're doing this before that.
Like I said,
your companies and I
have already decided this.
Not only will it help resolve the issues with our image,
but it'll also bring you guys closer together before filming actually begins.
Right,
this time...
I'm not sending any staff with you.
Why isn't that allowed?
Well, I want you guys...
to really spend some time together.
Uh, so what are we doing
on this trip, North?
Since that period
is exactly when we're releasing the pilot,
you'll be filming a reaction video
and some other content for us.
We're keeping the buzz alive.
Once you return, we're holding a blessing ceremony before filming.
Perfect timing.
We get to spend all day together, Wan.
Are you happy?
Without even entering any lucky draw.
Yes, Nine.
So where are we going?
Khao Yai.
[Present]
[Assumption University's Aquatic Center]
My dream might sound ordinary to someone else.
But for someone as sickly as me,
this is beyond what I'd ever dare to dream of.
[His health stands between him and his dream]
Wow...
Watch where you're going.
You're the new kid, right?
I'm Copter.
Hey, new kid.
Why did you drop out?
My name is Noel.
I didn't ask you that.
Then don't call me "new kid."
[A relationship blooms]
Just hold my hand if you want to.
I haven't set foot here in so long.
Why did you come back?
Why can't I?
This is somewhere I used to be.
I won't let you
be happy, Copter.
[A grudge from the past]
So now you wanna talk?
Leave Noel alone.
Noel, that new special someone of yours?
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Is this...
the promising young shark?
All I can see is a fucking loser.
You hate me
because you were gonna break up with Bas and fall for me?
[A decision between a dream and...]
Don't focus on anything else.
Just focus on swimming.
Well, that's all I want to focus on,
but...
[This love between us]
It's not like that, Noel.
Then what is it, Copter?
What did you say to Noel?
Are you angry?
Shut up!
I... like you.
[The Deep Between Us]
[Soon]
- Whoa... - Whoa.
Like, I can't wait for the series.
It looks like fun, right?
Third?
Right,
the series itself is so intense.
Please stay tuned.
I'm also...
feeling excited.
Noel's mommies, please don't get mad.
You were not behaving well.
You're gonna get it, Wan.
Alright,
please look forward to it.
Alright, lastly,
stay tuned for
'The Deep Between Us.'
See you soon.
See you.
- Bye-bye. - Bye-bye.
Cut...
Good job, boys.
You have one hour to rest.
Wan.
I think...
you're gonna blow up.
Mm, I think...
this scene was amazing.
It's work.
But it hurt for real.
That digital footprint will haunt you for life.
You're in trouble...
What?
I told you I didn't mean to.
Don't overthink that punching scene, Wan.
Everyone craves drama on set.
But I do think it's a win for you.
I'm jelly.
You stand out more than I do.
Not at all.
I definitely don't stand out more than the lead.
Jeez...
anyone and their mother
wants to see ThirdNine.
You never know, though...
It's showbiz, Wan.
Anything new is always all the rage.
That's true,
'cause how could I compare to you?
Right, guys.
I looked at the trending hashtags.
It made me so sad.
There was no "RenjiWan,"
only "ThirdNine"
and...
"ThirdWan,"
the hashtag that overtook "ThirdNine."
Seriously?
"Girl, ThirdWan is so hot right now."
It's pretty quiet, isn't it?
Wanna play a game?
I'll start.
Let's do hard-hitting questions.
For example...
Nine,
how did you feel when Wan told you he was your fan?
Honestly, it felt weird
when someone told you they were a fan of yours during a workshop.
However...
I didn't mind.
I'm sorry, Nine.
I didn't think it through that day.
Hey, it's fine.
You didn't cross the line or anything.
Plus...
you know how to carry yourself.
We're chill.
Alright.
Actually, there was one person who was displeased.
I remember...
Third asking,
"So people who don't put in effort deserve a chance?"
You were saying...
you wanted Wan removed from the project?
Mm... Yeah.
Only then, though.
Then...
Let me ask you, Wan.
Right now,
do you like me
or Third more?
Aren't you afraid of the answer?
Why would I be?
Wan says he's my fan, after all.
Of course, he likes me more.
Am I right?
Yes,
I like you just the same, Nine.
Come to think of it...
you haven't been asked, right, Time?
Can I ask you a question?
Say...
that day,
Renji's acting was atrocious,
but someone pulled some strings and he got the role.
How does that make you feel?
Nothing, actually.
Right...
that makes sense.
How could you feel anything
when...
you and Renji already knew each other, right?
Then, I'll go next.
Wan,
any thoughts on those who love throwing people under the bus?
They play the hero,
pretending to ask for help
when in reality, they're just a backstabber.
Why do you think they're doing that?
You're asking me?
But I'm not that kind of person.
I know.
You didn't do anything like that.
Wanna point the finger?
Then, let me ask you this.
You weren't cramping that day, were you?
Shit!
That's a hardball question.
It's not. I can answer it.
I asked you to massage my feet that day.
Did I look like I was fine?
Do you think I was gonna kill Wan?
Are you fucking nuts?!
Are you insane?
Why would I kill Wan?
No more questions?
Look at the camera. Three, two, one!
Nice.
One more time. Three, two, one!
Hold on just a second. Yeah.
Three, two...
Uh...
Renji, Wan, that's a wrap for you today.
Time, please come on set.
Why are you sitting here all stressed?
Is it about Nine?
Mm.
There must be something I did wrong.
Right!
Maybe it's because you and I are too close.
I don't think so.
Nine's not that invested in me.
But I don't want you to think that way.
You can like or love him,
but you have to love yourself, too.
How?
I can't give you the answers, either.
You and Nine...
Never mind. I won't ask.
You can ask.
No.
Why not?
Scared of the truth?
I've finished my cues.
I'm heading outside.
Where to?
Just sightseeing around here.
No...
They told us to stay here.
The worst that can happen is getting chewed out, no?
I'm off.
Hey, wait...
I'm coming with you.
Do you even know where I'm going?
No, so lead the way.
So eager to lead, too.
Ugh...
How did you find a place like this?
I overheard the staff talking.
You're a pretty nosy one.
Totally!
Living in the city,
whenever I feel stressed out,
I go for a motorcycle ride to feel the breeze on my face.
Though switching to a bicycle
gives me some peace of mind.
To me, the speed of a bicycle is just right.
You enjoy the ride and the view.
It's nice and relaxing.
I think I'm starting to like it.
Like what?
Everything.
Huh?
Good...
That way, you won't try to get me fired again.
Never once have I run off like this.
Am I gonna get chewed out when we get back?
If so, just defend me.
Is this actually your plan?!
To get me fired again, I meant.
Are you nuts?
You were the one running off.
I was just following you.
Oh, yeah.
You're right.
You're not being smart again.
You just insulted me again.
You're always foul-mouthing me.
You could say I'm insulting you.
But if you give it some thought,
I might just be helping you.
Help with what?
You were trying to get me fired back then.
It's true that I wanted you out back then,
but now, there's nowhere else I want you to be.
I like it...
It's like playing with a cat.
Uh...
A cat.
A real... cat.
Meow.
Meow...
Did you just say I'm as cute as a cat?
Mm...
Mmm...
What's that stance?
Hilarious.
Don't call me out!
So you do have a clumsy side.
I'm totally slick...
That's true.
Thank you for coming with me.
Mm.
Thank you, also,
for helping me conquer a new territory.
Conquer, huh?
Mm.
A bicycle ride?
Well, I've never done that before,
running off so suddenly.
Good thing we finished working;
otherwise, we'd be ditching work.
Lower your head for me.
Quick!
Good job
conquering it.
You pet me like a dog.
You're right.
One with soft fur.
This feels like a romantic scene, huh?
In a series...
the two male leads have gotta kiss now, right?
How?
This is how.
What a wuss.
Still think I'm a wuss?
There's a room available!
Why don't you get a room already?
Planning to tell the whole world?
You're both fucking assholes.
Are you gonna go explain yourself?
No,
I'm tired already.
You're getting better.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
Mm.
Oh, uh...
Pardon, could we skip the wireless mics?
I'm worried they might come off
and become dangerous.
I think...
the visuals can tell their own story,
and we'll make it fun.
Okay, we can skip that.
- Okay, thank you. - The rule is,
anyone whose strip of cloth is pulled off
will be eliminated.
The last one standing
is the winner.
Start!
Go follow someone else!
Nah!
Following you is the most fun.
Here comes Third!
Dumbass!
Hey!
Do you want the cloth or me?
What I want is...
The cloth?
Time, eliminated!
Just a split second.
I couldn't catch up with them.
I have no idea where they are.
Nine, I surrender.
Don't give up just yet.
You think I can't take it myself?
I'll battle to the end until I can claim it.
Are you trying to insult me?
Whoa, Nine?!
Are you okay?
Hey!
Wan fell.
Please come check on him.
You're okay, right?
Wan, eliminated.
What's up, bro?
Why are you running off?
What did you do wrong?
You're even more hated than I thought.
If you want it...
bow and pick it up.
No need to bow to you.
My foot will do the job.
Nine, eliminated!
Spending time with you guys is kinda entertaining.
Just the two of us left now.
Renji, eliminated!
Third is the winner!
We get to spend all day together, Wan.
Are you happy?
Without even entering any lucky draw.
I'm jelly.
You stand out more than I do.
Do you think I was gonna kill Wan?
Are you fucking nuts?!
Why don't you get a room already?
Planning to tell the whole world?
You're both fucking assholes.
Nine.
Nine, I'm sorry
my hand hit you in the face.
Your hand hitting my face?
What else?
About last night, I'm not sure...
if you'd believe me.
Honestly...
"You got it wrong."
Is that what you were gonna say?
Yes.
How convenient.
What else are you sorry for?
About #ThirdWan...
Why say sorry about that?
What for?
Actually, feel free to look at it this way.
So many people are on your side.
You're so good...
You did a dang great job.
[ThirdNine tying the cloth for each other; that's it, that's the moment #TheDeepOuting #ThirdNine]
[Why's there no sound? I need squealing #ThirdNine]
[The crumbs from ThirdNine sent Mommy into heart failure, fabulous #TheDeepOuting #ThirdNine]
[So why chase after each other, RenjiTime? Shippers would call it a ghost ship;
they fell into each other, awesome #TheDeepOuting #RenjiTime]
[The main couple got less screen time than the secondary one; what do you think? #ThirdNine #TheDeepOuting]
[So satisfied with that Nine and Wan scene; a big W when he snatched the cloth,
my baby boy's the best #TheDeepOuting #Ninenw]
[Where the hell is my RenjiWan? Enlighten me #TheDeepOuting #RenjiWan]
[Nine called the staff over to help Wan; what a male lead #TheDeepOuting #Ninenw]
[ThirdWan only; my baby boy is an angel, the male lead after all #TheDeepOuting #ThirdWan]
[Where's RenjiWan? Why is there even RenjiTime?
Do your homework, producers #TheDeepOuting]
[They ganged up on my boy; he was about to win, by the way #TheDeepOuting #Ninenw]
[1 #TheDeepOuting]
#TheDeepOuting just hit one million, Mr. North!
Woo!
Yes!
Maintain...
Maintain the pilot's hype.
Only five minutes after the photobook sneak peek dropped,
and the reposts are already over ten thousand!
#RenjiWan
is trending at No. 2.
Though... #ThirdNine
is hot on their heels.
Woo!
These kids really know the game!
A fan war between two groups of fans,
this is channeling the war
between the ThirdNine fandom and the RenjiWan fandom!
The more they fight, the more hype.
Until the blessing ceremony,
I'd like them
to remain trending,
okay?
Next,
I'd like everyone...
to chant prayers
to Lord Ganesha.
- Om Shri Ganeshaya Namah. - Om Shri Ganeshaya Namah.
Eat this first.
Huh?
Eat thong yip first,
so everything you touch turns to money, gold, and prosperity.
Are you secretly calling me money-hungry?
No.
It's hard to believe
you're the superstitious kind.
I heard it through word of mouth.
Uh... Wan.
Wan.
Uh, please step aside.
Like, step aside.
- Please. - Yeah.
Thank you.
Third, are you hot?
Hi...
Hi.
Wow, that's so cute!
So cute!
- Wan! - Wan!
Wan!
Renji, come here.
Go greet your fans.
Let's go greet your fans.
Come on.
Wan, keep going.
I'm here rooting for you today.
Ooh...
You're here to see me?
Yes, I'm here just for you.
Thank you.
Wan, Wan.
Thank you so much
for helping me the day I passed out.
Oh?
You're all good now, right?
How nice of you.
You're worried about me, right?
Yes.
Please take good care of yourself.
Thank you.
Alright!
Bye-bye...
- Bye-bye. - Bye-bye.
Anyway, allow me
to take the boys to the restroom.
Please adore Renji, too.
Absolutely!
- Wan, Wan. - Come on, kids.
Wave them goodbye.
- Let's go, kids. - Bye-bye.
- See you later. - Bye-bye, Wan. See ya.
- Wan... - Hm?
So many of your fans came today.
Mm,
I'm still on cloud nine.
Nice way to kick it off.
Congrats.
You have so many fans.
Probably from all the screen time you got in the pilot.
How lucky.
Was that playfulness or jealousy?
Sunny, Cher,
may I take photos of the boys for the official account?
Go...
Come on, let's take some photos.
Go take some pics.
Go on.
Alright.
Where do you want them?
Over there is fine.
Over there, you said?
Right there.
Scoot closer to each other.
Please go ahead.
Good job, Sunny.
So Wut isn't here?
You're here alone.
If he was, you would've seen him.
It just so happens that Wut
is taking Boom to Paris Fashion Week.
Didn't your boys get to go?
We have the whole team here.
Sunny,
could you answer on my behalf?
I don't wanna stoop to her level.
I get it.
Small companies
send their owners to work, huh?
- VE Entertainment. - VE Entertainment.
VE Entertainment.
Count me in.
It's teamwork.
Sunny, Cher,
We'll take the boys to an interview now.
Which boys?
Uh, we'll have...
Third and Nine.
Just ThirdNine?
Also, Renji and Wan.
"RenjiWan," too.
Absolutely.
Kids, go give an interview.
Third, Nine.
- Go. - This way, please.
Woo!
Did I hurt you with my nails?
Let's go.
Uh...
Miss,
what about me?
Uh, Time...
your name isn't on the list.
You're free to go.
Alright.
Wan.
What are you doing sitting here?
I wanna go home.
Tired?
What's going on?
Come on,
let's go see Cher
so we can hurry home.
Mama, look.
What?
Isn't Wan too lucky?
Rumor has it that
you wanted to give Wan the spotlight in the pilot?
Our intention has always been to give all four of them the spotlight.
It's just that...
Wan is truly blowing up,
which probably makes you think
that we're making him particularly famous on purpose.
But do we want Wan to become famous?
- We do, right? - Exactly.
Well... that'd be great.
Anyway, please stay tuned...
for 'The Deep Between Us.'
Scared Wan's gonna become more famous?
How fucking annoying. What do you want?
So you're not maintaining your image anymore?
Be careful, or people will see your true nature.
My true nature...
What about it?
It's fucked up. That's what.
You never want anyone to do better than you, anyway.
You seem so defensive over Wan, huh?
Yeah!
I don't want him to go through what I've been through.
What's the matter?
Traumatized?
Once again, you're playing the victim.
Don't test my patience.
I'm gonna expose you.
About what?
Someone like you wouldn't do that, bud.
If you would,
you would've done it ages ago.
One more thing.
You and I are an on-screen couple.
If I'm getting dragged, then you are, too.
You can prepare a nice fucking speech for your mom!
Enough!
Stop.
Renji, Wan...
They're not here, huh?
Uh...
VE Entertainment!
Bitch...
I don't need a ride home, Mama.
Someone's picking me up.
I'm going home by myself.
What do you think...
they're gonna expose about each other?
You said you wanted Wan to become famous?
You know how long I've been waiting for this.
Don't you think the villain is wearing too much makeup?
He's trying to steal the show for sure.
Wan.
Come with me.
Nine wants to have a word with you.
What the heck are you doing?!
You did amazing today.
Are you seriously complimenting me?
Thank you...
for saving me.
Please stop idolizing him.
I'm begging you...
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
♫I wanna let the world know, you wanna close it♫
♫Just wanna tell you, I'm doing fine, fine♫
♫You won't reveal it, but I won't conceal it♫
♫Trust me, it's alright♫
♫I know you don't like it, but what are you gonna do about it?♫
♫I'm not the one to blame if my heart says I should follow it♫
♫You can have anyone, I don't mind♫
♫I can like anyone, why shouldn't I?♫
♫They say it's not right, but I say it's alright♫
♫If you try ranking it♫
♫I'm on top of the list♫
♫I guess I have to do what I like♫
♫This heart won't ever follow advice♫
♫I don't wanna l-l-l-lie♫
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
♫You do you♫
♫You can love whoever♫
♫But I like you forever♫
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
♫No pressure, no drama♫
♫Hakuna Matata♫
♫Just somebody who likes ya♫
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
[Mr. Fanboy Series]